AKSARAPUK **MULLANE**

191 Overmount Ave, Woodland Park, NJ 🏚

+1 201-989-7291

amullane921@gmail.com ✓

linkedin.com/in/akmullane in



SUMMARY

Recent graduate of the Associate degree program in Computer Science from PCCC with a passion for computers and coding. Possesses two years of part-time experience in IT support at PCCC. Seeking opportunities in the field of software development or any role related to computers. Eager to apply knowledge and skills gained through education and work experience to contribute as a software developer or in any computer-related position.



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Nursing | Thammasat University, Thailand

DATES FROM MAY 2009 - TO MAY 2013

Graduated GPA: 3.15

Associate computer science | Passaic County community college

DATES FROM DECEMBER 2020 - MAY 2023

GPA: 4.00

Clubs and Societies: Computer and technology Club: Media manager, PTK member.



EXPERIENCE

IT help desk | Passaic County community college

DATES FROM JAN 2022- PRESENT

- Performing fast and efficient network support including troubleshooting, help desk functions, and correction of NT-related problems on servers and workstations
- Provide on-site support and troubleshooting of network equipment
- Assist employees via telephone, email, helpdesk tickets, and in-person requests
- Working with Corporate IT to resolve issues
- Install, make changes, and repair computer hardware and software
- Follow-up with customers to ensure issues are resolved
- Highly organized to keep Help desk tickets order
- Ability to diagnose and resolve basic computer technical issues

Computer lab tutor | Passaic County community college

DATES FROM FEBRUARY 2022- TO PRESENT

- Providing students positive and constructive feedback
- Demonstrating academic best practices for specific subjects and assignments, including research and coding tactics

• Working with students to help them understand key concepts, especially those learned in the classroom (For example, Python, and C++)

Fulfillment expert | Target corporation

DATES FROM NOVEMBER 2019- TO JANUARY 2023

- Select items for order pickup, drive up and ship to a home for digital guest orders
- Meet productivity metrics and other fulfillment goals
- Own your workspace and supplies; keep equipment and designated areas organized and supplies in stock
- Engage with guests in a genuine way, which includes asking questions to understand their specific needs better.
- Properly prepare, pack and sort guest orders for shipment using correct materials

Registered Nurse | Thammasat University Hospital (Thailand)

DATES FROM MAY 2013 - MAY 2016

- Monitoring vital signs, airway patency, and neurologic status
- Monitoring for possible complications
- Assessing and managing pain
- Assessing the surgical site (if relevant)
- Assessing and maintaining fluid and electrolyte balance
- Providing a thorough report of the patient's status to the receiving nurse on the recovery unit, as well as the patient's family.

Childcare provider | Private resident

DATES FROM MAY 2016 - JULY 2021

- Provides care to children inside and outside the home.
- Prepares healthy meals.
- Maintains daily schedule.
- Performs light housework.
- Leads children in fun activities.
- Keeps children's living and play areas tidy.
- Helps with homework and tutoring as needed.
- Cares for infants, including feeding, diapering, and dressing.
- Meets the physical, social, and emotional needs of children in their care.
- Provides structure and communicates consistent behavioral expectations.
- Encourages healthy habits and hygiene and helps with toilet training.
- Transports children, including school pickup and drop-off, play dates, and activities.



Phone support	45%	
Problem solving	45%	
Basic networking	35%	
Python	45%	
C++	55%	
Basic Computer	85%	
MS office	90	%
Troubleshooting	50%	